printrove.com 2016-04-25

# Printrove | Privacy Policy

It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

  1. **Personal information**

Before using certain parts of any Printrove.com (“Printrove”) or ordering Products, you must complete an online registration form. During registration, you will be prompted to provide to us certain personal information, including but not limited to User’s (your/company) name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address, and credit card number. In addition, we may also ask you for your/Customer’s country of residence and/or organization’s country of operation, so we can comply with applicable laws and regulations, and for your gender. These kinds of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill orders, to communicate about order and Printrove, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing the order, your personal information may be used to contact you.  
By registering at Printrove, you agree that all information provided in the registration data is true and accurate and that you will maintain and update this information as required in order to keep it current, complete, and accurate.  
Printrove may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its Site. Printrove may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Printrove does not disclose personal information other than as described here.  
If you are a registered user of a Printrove Site and have supplied your email address, Printrove may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, new Products, solicit your feedback. Printrove takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction personal information.

  2. **Disclosure of information**

Printrove discloses personal information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on Printrove’s behalf or to provide Services available at Printrove Site, and that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country.  
Printrove will not rent or sell personal information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described here, Printrove discloses personal information only in response to court order or other governmental request, or when Printrove believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Printrove, third parties or the public at large.

  3. **Security**

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

  4. **Cookies**

Printrove employs cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Most internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of Printrove Service. We have to use cookies to enable you to select Products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those Products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase.

  5. **Business transitions**

If Printrove, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the event that Printrove goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, your personal information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Printrove and/or the Site may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

  6. **Privacy policy changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Printrove may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Printrove’s sole discretion. Printrove encourages you to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this Site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
